Gorilla
大猩猩
歌手：Bruno Mars
压制：随Feng
她认为她骗了我 但我知道这是怎么回事
你在说什么
并不表现的如你所见那样 你没有看到她看着他的方式
她带着她的装束到这儿来 所有人都疯狂了
她可能以为他爱她
你和所有人都知道 没有人能陪着那个男孩躺下
好吧 如果新来的女孩认为她能在这里抢走我的生意
等着我告诉老板她和谁睡觉
你真坏
哦 不错
伊莎贝拉
你出场
女士们 先生们 接下来是个新来的女孩
大方的掏出你的钱来 让她感到。。。
温暖
来自丛林的
伊莎贝拉
Ooh I got a bottle full of liquor with a cocaine kicker
哦 酒精在我的血液里流窜 还夹带着兴奋剂的冲击
and i'm feeling like I'm thirty feet tall
我感觉自己像30尺巨人一样高大
So lay it down, lay it down
所以放下一切 所有一切
You got your legs up in the sky with the devil in your eyes
你将双腿伸向天际 歪念在你眼中流转
Let me hear you say you want it all
让我听见你大声说出 你想要一切
Say it now, say it now
说出来吧 就是现在
Look what you doing, look what you done
看看你现在在干什么 再看看你之前是怎么样的
But in this jungle you can't run
你已经无法逃离这片乱林
Cause what I got for you
因为我将要给你的绝对让你无法抗拒
I promise is a killer, you'll be banging on my chest
我的允诺如止痛药 你将一头撞进我的怀里
Bang bang, gorilla
砰 砰 就像大猩猩
You and me baby making love like gorillas
宝贝 你和我就像大猩猩般制造狂野的爱
Yeah I got a fistful of your hair
我不断爱抚你的头发
But you dont look like you're scared
你却没有丝毫恐惧
You're just smiling tell me daddy it's yours
面带笑容地告诉我 爹地 我是你的了
Cause you know how I like it use a dirty little lover
你知道我多么贪恋着一切 你真是令人怜爱的小骚货
If the neighbors call the cops call the sheriff, call the SWAT
即使邻居通知警察 通知警长 镇暴部队
we don't stop
我们也不会停下
we keep rocking while they knocking on our door
继续疯狂巫山云雨 任由他们敲门
And you're screaming give it to me baby
你会狂喊 加把劲吧贱人
Give it to me matherfucker
快使出你的浑身解数
Ohhh look what you doing, look what you done
哦 再看看你之前是怎么样的
But in this jungle you can't run
你已经无法逃离这片乱林
Cause what I got for you
因为我给你带来了你要的
I promise is a killer, you'll be banging on my chest
我的允诺如止痛药 你将一头撞进我的怀里
Bang bang, gorilla
砰 砰 就像大猩猩
You and me baby making love like gorillas
宝贝 你和我就像大猩猩般制造狂野的爱
I bet you never ever felt so good, so good
我打赌你从未体会过这种极致快感 真爽
I got your body trembling like it should, it should
我让你的身体不由自主地颤抖 仿佛这是本能
You'll never be the same baby once im done with you
你将会脱胎换骨 宝贝 我和你一起享受这一刻
Woooh Woooh Woooh Woooh
Oh you with me baby making love like gorillas
宝贝 你和我就像大猩猩般制造狂野的爱
You and me baby we'll be fucking it like gorillas
Yeah Yeah Baby Fucking Oh Yeah
You and me baby making love like gorillas
宝贝 你和我就像大猩猩般制造狂野的爱
压制：随Feng